Kill the boy
Mata al niño
and let the man be born.
y deja que nazca el hombre.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; I just hit my door on that [__]
Acabo de golpear mi puerta con esa [ __ ].
&gt;&gt; Back, baby. Let's see what we're looking
De vuelta, nena.  Veamos qué tenemos
at today.
hoy.   Es
It's one of those days, man. We woke up
uno de esos días, tío.  Nos despertamos
and I
y
I thought to myself, you know what? I
pensé para mis adentros, ¿sabes qué?  Me
love the McLaren wrap, right? The
encanta el vinilo de McLaren, ¿verdad?  El
McLaren wrap's great. It's cool. I've
diseño del McLaren es genial.  Es genial.  Lo tengo desde hace mucho
had it for so long, but it kind of feels
tiempo, pero ya me parece un poco
outdated. It feels like I've I've had it
anticuado.  Siento que lo he tenido durante demasiado tiempo
for just a little bit too long. And
.  Y
today, I'm going to take the McLaren in
hoy voy a llevar el McLaren al taller
to get fixed and re-wrapped in a very
para que lo reparen y le pongan un vinilo con un
special print that I know a lot of you
estampado muy especial que sé que a muchos de ustedes les
guys are going to [__] hate. But,
va a encantar.  Pero no pasa nada
that's okay. It's my car. It's my life,
.  Es mi coche.  Es mi vida
and I don't give a
y me da igual.
Open it up, bro. Damn.
Ábrelo, hermano.  Maldición.
Pa ra ra ra.
Pa ra ra ra.
Wait till I get my money right. Put that
Espera a que tenga mi dinero en orden.  Pon eso
on boom.
en boom.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; All right, look at this [__] though.
Vale, mira esta [ __ ].   Ya era hora
It's just overdue, bro. Like, I don't
, hermano.  Como, no
know. I've had this for like 2 years
sé.  Lo tengo desde hace unos dos años
now. I'm just like, it's cool. It's
.  Yo simplemente pienso: es genial.  Es
pink. It's purple. I love it. Snake
rosa.  Es morado.  Me encanta.
skin, but we got to switch it up. I'm
Piel de serpiente, pero tenemos que cambiarlo.  Me está empezando a
getting a little bored of it. Instead of
aburrir un poco.  En lugar de
going to buy a new car, which I do every
ir a comprar un auto nuevo, cosa que hago todas las
week, instead, I'm going to actually
semanas, en vez de eso, voy a ponerlo a punto. Hay
tune I'm going to There's a few things
algunas cosas que
we're going to do. Let's talk about it,
vamos a hacer.  Hablemos de ello, ¿de
right? We have a dent right here. So,
acuerdo?  Tenemos una abolladura justo aquí.  Así que, puede que
you guys might not know what that's
no sepan de dónde viene eso
from. Let me explain. A year and a half
.  Permítanme explicarles.  Hace un año y medio
ago, someone broke into my house, took
, alguien entró en mi casa, se llevó
all of my keys, took my Lamborghini,
todas mis llaves, se llevó mi Lamborghini, dio marcha atrás y chocó
reversed it into my [__] McLaren,
contra mi maldito McLaren, y
drove off with the Lamborghini. Police
se fue conduciendo el Lamborghini.
came. I had to go find the Lamborghini.
Llegó la policía.  Tuve que ir a buscar el Lamborghini.
All kinds of [__] I'll play the
Todo tipo de tonterías.  Voy a reproducir el
clip. That was a while ago, but you guys
vídeo.  Eso fue hace tiempo, pero
can see the video right there.
pueden ver el video justo ahí.   ¿
Does somebody you know? No. No.
Alguien que conoces?  No. No.
No, they were in all black black masks
No, estaban todos negros, máscaras negras
and everything.
y todo.
So the security guards let them in then.
Entonces los guardias de seguridad los dejaron entrar.
Yeah.
Sí.
Yeah, they're
Sí, lo son. Vaya
Woah, they got in the Maybach, too? Man,
, ¿ellos también se subieron al Maybach?  Hombre,
we're going to get the dent fixed. The
vamos a arreglar la abolladura.  El
wing is still stuck back there and it
ala sigue atascada ahí atrás y
won't come up, so we're going to get
no sube, así que vamos a
that fixed. Then, from there, we're
arreglarla.  Luego, a partir de ahí, lo vamos
going to tune it, we're going to mod it,
a ajustar, lo vamos a modificar, lo
we're going to make it louder, faster,
vamos a hacer más fuerte, más rápido,
we're going to make it sound like a
vamos a hacer que suene como un
[__] firecracker when you can
maldito petardo cuando puedas
take your foot off the gas and it's like
quitar el pie del acelerador y es como
Hopefully it doesn't sound like that.
Esperemos que no suene así.
Sounds like I got
Parece que tengo
flu or something. And then we're going
gripe o algo así.  Y luego vamos
to get this re-wrapped, okay? [music] So
a volver a envolverlo, ¿de acuerdo?  [música] Así que
we're going to take this to McLaren
vamos a llevar esto a McLaren ahora mismo
right now, maybe look at some other
, tal vez mirar otros
McLarens for fun, and maybe buy a
McLaren por diversión, y tal vez comprar un
couple, huh? Let's get it.
par, ¿eh?  Vamos a conseguirlo.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
[singing]
[cantando]
&gt;&gt; That's a Pagani. Bro. 720, Urus, that's
Ese es un Pagani.  Hermano.  720, Urus, ese es
the i8, GT3, and then the Cullinan.
el i8, GT3 y luego el Cullinan.
I have another Rolls at home, too, but
También tengo otro Rolls en casa, pero
yeah.
sí.
Yeah. We've been working here for a
Sí.  Llevamos trabajando aquí un
while. I've never seen this Yeah. We
tiempo.  Nunca había visto esto. Sí.  Nos
just moved here like 2 weeks ago.
mudamos aquí hace apenas dos semanas.   ¿De
Where'd you come from? Uh my mom's
dónde vienes?  Eh, la vagina de mi mamá
vagina, but
, pero
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[risas]
&gt;&gt; Bro.
Hermano.
No, we came from We live out here, just
No, venimos de aquí. Vivimos aquí, justo al
down the street. I just needed more
final de la calle.  Simplemente necesitaba más
room. I had too many cars at the house,
espacio.  Tenía demasiados coches en casa,
so we're like we'll get a little
así que pensamos en comprar un pequeño
warehouse. Yeah, we're going to add a
almacén.  Sí, también vamos a añadir una
deck and [__] too. It'll be cool.
cubierta y esas cosas.  Será genial.   ¿
What's up, bro?
Qué pasa, hermano?   ¿
How you doing, bro?
Cómo estás, hermano?
Dog, I'm not mad about this place.
Perro, no estoy enfadado con este sitio.
Good. How you doing, bro? Good, bro.
Bien.  ¿Cómo estás, hermano?  Bien, hermano.
Good. So we got your Rolex. He's got
Bien.  Así que ya tenemos tu Rolex.  Tiene
your Rolex. [music] Let's get it. I
tu Rolex.  [música] ¡Vamos a por ello!
forgot we were about to go drop off the
Olvidé que íbamos a dejar el
McLaren and I forgot I ordered some
McLaren y olvidé que había pedido algunos
watches, so let's take a look real
relojes, así que echemos un vistazo
quick, man. Shout out Happy Jewelers,
rápido, tío.  Un saludo a Happy Jewelers,
man. Okay, let's see watch number one.
tío.  Bien, veamos el reloj número uno.
Oh.
Oh.
[__]
[ __ ].   ¿
You ready for this?
Estás preparado para esto?
Stupid.
Estúpido.
That is stupid, bro. I mean, is that
Eso es estúpido, hermano.  Es decir, ¿eso es
even legal? Put the Richard Mille down,
siquiera legal?  Deja el Richard Mille,
that little piece of [__]
esa pequeña [ __ ].
Put on some of these Rolexes. That's so
Ponte alguno de estos Rolex.  Qué
nice. Jeez.
bonito.  Dios mío.
Luckily, that one's already a perfect
Por suerte, ese ya encaja a la perfección
fit.
.
&gt;&gt; Yeah, I sized them up to Ali. Oh, okay.
Sí, los comparé con Ali.  Ah, okey.   Sí
&gt;&gt; like, yeah, y'all got about the same
, todos tenéis más o menos la misma
[music] wrist. Yeah, same wrist,
muñeca [musical].  Sí, la misma muñeca,
different weiner size.
diferente tamaño de pene.
&gt;&gt; all good. That's awesome. Can you see
todo está bien.  Eso es genial.  ¿Puedes ver
that? Is that doing it justice in there
eso?  ¿Eso no le hace justicia
or what? All right, watch number one.
o qué?  Muy bien, mira el número uno.
That shit's beautiful. All right, that's
Esa [ __ ] es hermosa.  Vale, esa es
probably my favorite one. She started
probablemente mi favorita.  Empezó
with that one last, but it's okay. All
con esa al final, pero está bien.
right, what else do we got, bro?
Vale, ¿qué más tenemos, hermano?
Rose gold two-tone.
Bicolor oro rosa.
Rose gold two-tone. What is that, a
Bicolor oro rosa.  ¿Qué es eso, una
chocolate face? Yeah, that's nasty, bro,
cara de chocolate?  Sí, eso es asqueroso, tío,
with the diamonds. Ah, beautiful,
con los diamantes.  Ah, hermoso,
beautiful. I love that. Last but not
hermoso.  Me encanta eso.  Por último, pero no
least,
menos importante,
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[risas]
&gt;&gt; watch your eyes and watch your
cuida tus ojos y cuida a tu
girlfriend. Shout out Happy Jewelers,
novia.  Un saludo a Happy Jewelers,
man. Once again, picking up three
tío.  Una vez más, ¡te llevas tres
Rolexes, man. If you guys are ever in
Rolex!  Si alguna vez están en el
Orange County, Happy Jewelers [music] is
Condado de Orange, Happy Jewelers [música] es
the place to be. If you're ever in
el lugar al que deben ir.  Si alguna vez están en
California, cuz I don't know any other
California, porque no conozco ningún otro
places that are
lugar que sea
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[cantando]
[music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; All right, guys. So, good news, we got
Muy bien, chicos.  Buenas noticias: conseguimos
the dent out of the McLaren. The
quitar la abolladura del McLaren.  El
McLaren's wing has officially been
alerón del McLaren ya ha sido
fixed. This is some crazy [__] There
reparado oficialmente.  Esto es una locura.
was a Rolls-Royce key stuck [music]
Había una llave de Rolls-Royce atascada [música]
inside the wing. That's why it wasn't
dentro del ala.  Por eso no bajaba
going down. When you're rich, you just
.  Cuando eres rico,
be losing [__] you be losing keys.
pierdes cosas, pierdes las llaves.
There's cars stuck inside of other cars.
Hay coches atascados dentro de otros coches.
It's ridiculous, but good news is all
Es ridículo, pero la buena noticia es que todo
that got fixed. Bad [music] news is is
eso se solucionó.  La mala noticia [musical] es que
I'm sick as [__] Like, 10 out of 10,
estoy jodidamente enfermo.  Como un 10 sobre 10, a punto
ready to pass the [__] out, but it is
de desmayarme, pero es lo que hay
what it is. We got to keep going. This
.  Tenemos que seguir adelante.  Esto
is what I do. I'd like to show you guys
es lo que hago.  Me gustaría mostrarles
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música] que
&gt;&gt; the dent is gone. We now just have to
la abolladura ya no está.  Ahora solo tenemos que volver a
get it re-wrapped, but before we get it
envolverlo, pero antes de
re-wrapped in a very special, particular
volver a envolverlo con un envoltorio muy especial y particular
wrap, [music] we have to take it to
, [música] tenemos que llevarlo a
another shop, get this thing down piped
otro taller, bajarle el escape
and tuned, so that way it sounds
y afinarlo, para que suene como si valiera
like a million dollars. Let's go, baby.
un millón de dólares.  Vamos, cariño.
Let's get [music] it tuned. It's only
Vamos a afinar [la música].  Solo
going to cost about 15 grand, so
va a costar unos 15 mil dólares, así que es
something cheap to do to your car if you
algo barato que hacerle a tu coche si
guys ever have 15 grand lying around.
alguna vez tenéis 15 mil dólares de sobra.
[music] Get your [__] tuned, man. Let's
[música] Pon a punto tu [ __ ], tío.  Vamos a
get it.
conseguirlo.
&gt;&gt; [snorts]
[resopla]
&gt;&gt; Life has gotten so good.
La vida se ha vuelto tan buena.   ¿
Right? You take your McLaren to the shop
Bien?  Llevas tu McLaren al taller
to get tuned. You're going to put about
para que le hagan una puesta a punto.  Vas a invertir unos
$30,000 into taking it and turning it
30.000 dólares en transformarlo
into the beast you want to make it. And
en la bestia que quieres que sea.  Y
on your way there, you have to have your
de camino allí, tu
manager follow you and your Lamborghini
gerente tiene que seguirte a ti y a tu
truck to pick you up because you're
camioneta Lamborghini para recogerte porque vas a
dropping off your $400,000, $370,000 I
dejar tu McLaren de 400.000 dólares, o mejor dicho, de 370.000 dólares
should say, McLaren. That's when you
.  Ahí es cuando lo lograste, hijo de [ __ ]
[__] made it. There's my Lambo
.  Ahí arriba está mi Lambo
up there. Kind of far ahead of me. He's
.  Está bastante adelantado a mi tiempo.  Está
driving like a maniac, but
conduciendo como un loco, pero ya
you know,
sabes,
&gt;&gt; [music]
[la música]
&gt;&gt; it is what it is, man. Life's good.
es lo que es, hombre.  La vida es buena.   La
Life's very good. And then I get to get
vida es muy buena.  Y luego puedo subirme a
in my Urus, drive back to my warehouse
mi Urus, conducir de regreso a mi almacén
where I have my Pagani, my GT3RS, my
donde tengo mi Pagani, mi GT3RS, mi
SVJ, my i8, my Rolls-Royce Wraith, my
SVJ, mi i8, mi Rolls-Royce Wraith, mi
Rolls-Royce Cullinan, and my Rolls-Royce
Rolls-Royce Cullinan y mi Rolls-Royce
Ghost.
Ghost.
That's life.
Así es la vida.
Well,
Bueno,
I ain't going to lie to you boys, man.
no les voy a mentir, muchachos.
I just hit my door on that [__] Pretty
Acabo de golpear mi puerta con esa [ __ ].  Bastante
hard, too. So,
difícil también.  Entonces,
Oh, yeah. Look.
oh, sí.  Mirar.   ¿
See the little piece? Now I got to buy
Ves el pedacito?  Ahora tengo que comprar
another one. Damn it. I need you to
otro.  [ __ ] sea.  Necesito que me
order me a 750S, bro.
pidas una 750S, hermano.   ¿
What the [__] My favorite car ever, but
Qué [ __ ]?  Mi coche favorito de todos los tiempos, pero
it has so many issues. It's kind of
tiene muchísimos problemas.  Es un poco
ridiculous. We just got it fixed. Air
ridículo.  Acabamos de arreglarlo.  El aire
conditioning [music] instantly not
acondicionado [música] dejó de
working again. Super hot air coming out.
funcionar de nuevo.  Sale aire muy caliente.
There's always something with these
Siempre hay algo con estos
McLarens, bro. It's my favorite car to
McLaren, hermano.  Es mi coche favorito para
drive, but in terms of issues, it's got
conducir, pero en cuanto a problemas, tiene
a new issue literally probably every
un problema nuevo prácticamente cada
week. So, it is what it is. Whatever.
semana.  Así son las cosas.  Lo que sea.
Just going to have to pay for new air
Tendremos que volver a pagar por un aire
conditioning again, but summer's coming
acondicionado nuevo, pero
up, too. But, this bad [__] right here
además se acerca el verano.  Pero, esta zorra de aquí
though. It's time to turn it up.
.  Es hora de subir el volumen.
Yeah.
Sí.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; I'm a boss. How you doing, man? Was I
Soy un jefe.  ¿Cómo estás, tío?  ¿Estaba
talking with you the phone? Yeah, yeah.
hablando contigo por teléfono?  Sí, sí.
That was my manager and me, but yeah.
Éramos mi representante y yo, sí.
Okay, cool. Yeah, [music] we're going to
Vale, genial.  Sí, [música] vamos a
make this thing sound like a million
hacer que esto suene como si valiera un millón de
bucks or what? Yeah. Yeah, let's do it,
dólares, ¿o qué?  Sí.  Sí, hagámoslo,
bro. That's the key. Cool. Um what do
hermano.  Esa es la clave.  Fresco.  ¿Qué
you guys Do you guys need anything right
necesitan
now? A deposit, [music] you said?
ahora mismo?  ¿Un depósito, [música] dijiste?
&gt;&gt; Good morning. Okay. I got to ask for
Buen día.  Bueno.  Tengo que pedir
turbos and wing on.
turbos y alerón.
&gt;&gt; Awesome. Complicated or no? It'll be
Impresionante.  ¿Complicado o no?  Será
fun.
divertido.   Es
It's a little complicated. It's a fat
un poco complicado.  Es un
ass, like front end's big. Yeah. Got a
culo gordo, como si la parte delantera fuera grande.  Sí.  Tiene un
big hood.
capó grande.   Se
&gt;&gt; it opens up and it's like all flamed
abre y es como si todo se apagara
out, yeah. [music] You didn't realize
, sí.  [música] No te habías dado cuenta de que es
it's an Aventador. Wow, it's an Aston
un Aventador.  ¡Guau, es un Aston
Martin. Very nice car. You guys going to
Martin!  Un coche muy bonito.  ¿Van a
have to put some Make that that
tener que poner algo de... Hagan que ese
Rolls-Royce loud right there? I mean, if
Rolls-Royce de ahí suene fuerte?  Es decir, si
they wanted to. Can you? It has
quisieran.  ¿Puede?  Tiene una
surprising power for as much vehicle as
potencia sorprendente para un vehículo de este tamaño
it is. It'll growl and everything?
.  ¿Gruñirá y todo eso?   Podría ser
It could. Get it to pop? I got three
.  ¿Hacer que explote?  Tengo tres
Rolls-Royces. They're all quiet as hell.
Rolls-Royce.  Todos están callados como el infierno.
But, if I can get the Wraith to sound
Pero si pudiera conseguir que el Wraith sonara
like a Lamborghini, I'd do it.
como un Lamborghini, lo haría.
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[risas] ¿
&gt;&gt; What is this right here? That's not
Qué es esto de aquí?  Ese no es
SF90, is it? Yeah, we're doing
SF90, ¿verdad?  Sí, ¿vamos a hacer
&gt;&gt; 48? 488?
48?  488?
Beautiful car. Ferrari's probably going
Hermoso coche.
to be next for me, I think. [music] Aw,
Creo que mi próximo coche probablemente será un Ferrari.  [música] Ay,
this reminds me of my Huracan. Oh my
esto me recuerda a mi Huracán.  Ay
god. Is this
dios mío.  ¿Es esto?
Oh,
Oh,
I miss my Huracan. I I mean, I love the
extraño mi Huracán.  Quiero decir, me encanta el
SVJ, don't get me wrong, but what I love
SVJ, no me malinterpreten, pero lo que me encanta
about the Huracan is it drives smoother
del Huracán es que se conduce con más suavidad
than SVJ. Just take off, it doesn't jump
que el SVJ.  Simplemente despega, no
on you and get crazy, you know what I'm
te salta encima y se vuelve loco, ¿entiendes lo que
saying? Maybe I'll get a Huracan Spyder
digo?  Quizás pronto vuelva a comprarme un Huracán Spyder
again soon. Keep the SVJ though and the
.  Eso sí, quédate con el SVJ y el
Urus, obviously. I have three Lambos,
Urus, obviamente.  Tengo tres Lamborghinis,
but
pero
I like this a lot. [music]
este me gusta mucho.  [música]
SS Auto Performance, baby. We're getting
SS Auto Performance, nena.  Vamos a hacer
a full tour.
una visita guiada completa.
Oh [__] Oh my gosh, bro. This is
Oh, [ __ ].  ¡Dios mío, hermano!  Esto es
badass.
genial.
Then we got the lounge. Woo!
Luego nos dieron el salón.  ¡Cortejar!
We got the lounge to hang out, couches
Tenemos un salón para relajarse, con sofás
you can just fall asleep in if you can't
en los que puedes quedarte dormido si no puedes evitarlo
help yourself. It
.
It makes me feel like [__] about my
Me hace sentir fatal con respecto a mi
warehouse. You got to get this in the
almacén.  Tienes que conseguir esto en el
warehouse. Yeah. Yeah, we do. Yeah, we
almacén.  Sí.  Sí, lo hacemos.  Sí, lo hacemos
do. This makes my warehouse look like
.  Esto hace que mi almacén parezca como si fuera a
like I'm going to buy this whole
comprar toda la
company, take all the cars out and we're
empresa, sacar todos los coches y quedarnos solo con
going to just have this warehouse. This
este almacén.  Este
is dude a little bar That's a beautiful
es un pequeño bar, amigo. Ese es un
car.
coche precioso.
Wow, that's [__] beautiful. We pull
Vaya, eso es jodidamente hermoso.  Lo desmontamos
it all apart. Doors doors come off.
todo.  Las puertas se quitan.
Everything comes out that needs to come
Todo sale a la luz para que
out so we can do [music]
podamos hacer [música]
all the jams. We can bury all of this so
todas las jam sessions.  Podemos ocultar todo esto para que
you can't tell. You can hear me right
no te des cuenta.  Puedes oírme ahora mismo
now.
.
This is what it's going to sound like
Así es como sonará
soon on the McLaren. Holy [__]
pronto en el McLaren.  ¡[ __ ]!
That's brutal. See what this thing's
Eso es brutal.  ¿Ya ves de qué se
about, ready?
trata esto? ¿Estás listo?
All right boys, we are on our way back
Muy bien, chicos, ya estamos de regreso
[music] to pick up the McLaren. Man,
[música] para recoger el McLaren.  ¡Vaya, nos
they sent us a little a little teaser of
enviaron un pequeño adelanto!
it. It's hard to tell on camera, but it
Es difícil apreciarlo en cámara, pero
sounds pretty damn good to me. We're
a mí me suena bastante bien.
going to pick up this car, take it to
Vamos a recoger este coche, llevarlo
the warehouse, rev the [__] out of the
al almacén, acelerar a fondo el
[__] engine, get the whole warehouse
motor, prender fuego a todo el almacén
on fire, call the ambulance, extinguish
, llamar a la ambulancia, apagar
the fire, and then buy 10 more cars cuz
el fuego y luego comprar 10 coches más porque
they're all going to be damaged, but
todos van a quedar dañados, pero
we're going to find out what this thing
vamos a averiguar cómo
sounds like and next step is to get it
suena este y el siguiente paso es
wrapped and the final product will be
forrarlo y el producto final estará
here. Let's get it.
aquí.  Vamos a conseguirlo.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; Closed on Sunday.
Cerrado los domingos.
You my Chick-fil-A.
Tú eres mi Chick-fil-A.
You [music] my Chick-fil-A.
Tú [música] mi Chick-fil-A.
Hold the selfies.
Dejen de hacerse selfies.
Put the drag baby. Let's see what we're
Pon el drag nena.  Veamos qué tenemos
looking at today. If I take this walk
hoy.  Si hago este camino
alone
solo, me inclino
bow [music] down to the king upon the
[música] ante el rey en el
throne
trono, la
life is his I'm no longer
vida es suya, ya no soy
[music and singing] my own. So we're
[música y canto] mío.  Así que estamos a punto de
about to pretty much do a little test.
hacer una pequeña prueba.
He's going to rev a regular McLaren
Va a acelerar un McLaren normal de
stock and then he's going to rev my
serie y luego va a acelerar mi
McLaren now that it's been tuned and
McLaren ahora que ha sido modificado y
we're going to hear the difference in
vamos a escuchar la diferencia en
the audio compared to a stock and
el audio en comparación con uno de serie y
obviously my tuned
obviamente mi
McLaren is going to be doing.
McLaren modificado va a estar haciendo.
That's very nice.
Eso es muy agradable.   Esa
So that's a setting though. So if you
es una configuración.  Así que si
don't want it to do it, it won't.
no quieres que lo haga, no lo hará.
&gt;&gt; Okay. Good. Good. So if you want to come
Bueno.  Bien.  Bien.  Entonces, si quieres llegar de forma discreta
in low-key and you just want to drive
y simplemente quieres conducir con
normal Okay. 100%. Okay. Then when you
normalidad, está bien.  100%.  Bueno.  Luego, cuando
want to do it, you switch the map.
quieras hacerlo, cambias el mapa.
&gt;&gt; Okay. Okay. So you're not you're not
Bueno.  Bueno.  Así que no eres tú, no eres
like So if there's a cop nearby, I could
como Si hay un policía cerca, podría
turn it down.
bajarle el volumen.
Little difference.
Poca diferencia.
They're not similar.
No son similares.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
[music]
[música] ¿
&gt;&gt; So I just push it up or I got to hold
Entonces solo tengo que empujarlo hacia arriba o tengo que mantener presionado
the button? away from you Then up? And
el botón?  lejos de ti ¿Entonces arriba?  Y
then up and down. All right. Nothing to
luego arriba y abajo.  Está bien.  ¿No hay nada para
lock it at? We're good? That's it.
bloquearlo?  ¿Estamos bien?  Eso es todo.
Figure it out.
Descúbrelo.   Está bien
All right.
.
Keep brakes on. That'll be fun.
Mantén los frenos puestos.  Eso será divertido.
Awesome.
Impresionante.
Oh, that's loud.
Oh, eso es ruidoso.
HELLO.
Hola.   ¿
WHAT IS IT?
Qué es?
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[risas] No
&gt;&gt; IT WOULDN'T STOP.
paraba.   ¿En serio
BRO, are kidding me?
, tío?
So, we just got to it's just going to
Entonces, ¿simplemente tenemos que decir que va a
[__] crackle and pop every time I let
crujir y estallar cada vez que lo suelte así
go like that? That's [__] beautiful.
?  Eso es jodidamente hermoso.   Me
I love it. I literally love it.
encanta.  Me encanta, literalmente.   ¿Qué? ¿Me estás tomando el pelo
Are you kidding me right now, man? Yeah,
, tío?  Sí, será
you better put that [__] on, man. I'm
mejor que te pongas esa [ __ ], tío.  Voy
about to drive this thing like a maniac,
a conducir esta cosa como un loco,
bro.
hermano.   ¡
Oh my god, dude. The cops are going to
Dios mío, tío!  A la policía le va a
hate this thing. That's mad. That's
encantar esto.  Eso es una locura.  Eso es una locura
[__] mad, bro. My gosh.
, tío.  Dios mío.
This is America.
Esto es Estados Unidos.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; Don't catch you slipping now.
No te pillo desprevenido ahora.
Look what I'm whipping now.
Mira lo que estoy haciendo ahora.   Ya
We are officially in the warehouse.
estamos oficialmente en el almacén.
We're going to rev the [__] out of this
Vamos a acelerar a fondo esta
thing and let's see if we can get some
cosa y a ver si conseguimos que salgan
flames to come out. Go ahead.
llamas.  Adelante.
Oh.
Oh.
&gt;&gt; Going to show you guys, but I'm going to
Voy a mostrarles, chicos, que voy a
be closing this US 30 trade that I got
cerrar esta operación con US 30 en la que entré hace un rato
into a little bit earlier today. It's
hoy.  Se trata de una
about $34,000 in profit. We're going to
ganancia de unos 34.000 dólares.  Vamos a
close this position. 1 2. That'll pay
cerrar esta posición.  1 2. Eso pagará
for not only the tune, but the wrap
no solo la melodía, sino también el vinilo
[music] and everything else that we had
[música] y todo lo demás que tuvimos que
to do to the McLaren. Again, that's why
hacerle al McLaren.  Por eso
I love trading. That's why I love trade.
me encanta operar en bolsa.  Por eso me encanta el comercio.
I can trade from my phone anywhere,
Puedo operar desde mi teléfono en cualquier lugar,
[music] make money, provide for my
[música] ganar dinero, mantener a mi
family, buy a bunch of cars I love, get
familia, comprar un montón de autos que me encantan,
them wrapped, get them tuned, have a
rotularlos, ponerlos a punto, pasarlo bien
great time. You know, a lot of you guys
.  Como saben, muchos de ustedes
don't have the time to learn to become a
no tienen el tiempo para aprender a ser
trader or the patience that it takes to
operadores bursátiles ni la paciencia necesaria para
get there. And I get that. That's why
lograrlo.  Y lo entiendo.  Por eso
I've created a program where you can
he creado un programa donde puedes
literally copy every trade I take. And
copiar literalmente cada operación que realizo.  Y además
it's very affordable. And anybody can
es muy asequible.  Y cualquiera puede
afford it. It's actually $39.99, which
permitírselo.  En realidad cuesta 39,99 dólares, un
is similar to the cost of Hulu, Netflix,
precio similar al de una suscripción a Hulu, Netflix
or gym membership. So, for $39.99, you
o a un gimnasio.  Así que, por 39,99 dólares,
can copy every single trade that I take
puedes copiar todas y cada una de las operaciones que realizo
and pretty much just get the same
y obtener prácticamente los mismos
results as me. I mean, very no-brainer
resultados que yo.  Es decir, una
type of decision to make. Check out all
decisión obvia.  Mira todos
of these testimonials, man. But, now I
estos testimonios, tío.  Pero ahora me
would love to get into the reveal
encantaría hablarles de la presentación
of the brand new and improved McLaren
del nuevo y mejorado McLaren
720S. You guys ready for this? See you
720S.  ¿Están listos para esto?  Nos vemos al
on the other side.
otro lado.   ¿
What do you guys think?
Qué opináis?   Es como
&gt;&gt; the Super Bowl, but the difference is
el Super Bowl, pero la diferencia es que son
it's just two guys [music] playing [__]
solo dos tipos [de música] tocando cosas
that they did in the studio. [__]
que hicieron en el estudio.
usually send their verses back to me and
Normalmente, los tíos me devuelven sus versos y son
they'd be terrible like a 2-year-old.
horribles, como los de un niño de dos años.
[music] I love a dinner with some fine
[música] Me encanta una cena con unas buenas
women when they start debating about
mujeres cuando empiezan a debatir sobre
[singing] who the goat. I'm like, "Go
[cantando] quién es la cabra.  Yo le dije: "Adelante,
ahead. Say it then." [music]
dilo entonces".  [música]
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música] ¿Tan
&gt;&gt; Big as the what?
grande como qué?   ¿Tan
Big as the what?
grande como qué?   Tan
Big as the Super Bowl. [__] so thirsty
grande como el Super Bowl.  Los negros están tan sedientos
to put me in a beat. So, I mean,
de ponerme en un ritmo.  Bueno,
obviously I could have went with another
obviamente podría haber optado por otro
basic wrap. Could have went red, [music]
envoltorio básico.  Podría haber sido rojo, [música]
yellow, purple. I could have just done a
amarillo, morado.  Podría haber optado por un
regular color, all black, all white.
color normal, todo negro, todo blanco.
But, I was thinking, you know what? I'm
Pero estaba pensando, ¿sabes qué?  Soy
a Louis Vuitton wearing ass cracker. Why
un imbécil que usa Louis Vuitton.  ¿Por qué
would I not get a Louis Vuitton McLaren
no iba a comprarme un McLaren de Louis Vuitton
to go with this? This is a one-of-one,
para que hiciera juego con esto?  Este es un McLaren 720S único,
never seen before, never done before
nunca antes visto, nunca antes realizado
McLaren 720S. Look at the [__] beauty
.  Mira qué belleza tan jodida.
that this is. Not only does it go with
No solo combina con la
half of my clothing collection, but when
mitad de mi colección de ropa, sino que cuando
you see this on the road and you hear
ves esto en la calle y lo oyes
this on the road, you say, "That's a
en la calle, dices: "Ese es un
rich [__] in there." And that's
hijo de [ __ ] rico".  Y eso es
exactly what we're going for with this
precisamente lo que buscamos con este
build. So, beautiful, beautiful car, one
proyecto.  Así que, un coche precioso, único en su clase
of a kind, favorite build yet, favorite
, mi proyecto favorito hasta ahora, mi
wrap yet. I mean, the car in total is my
vinilado favorito hasta ahora.  Quiero decir, el coche en su conjunto es mi
favorite car. It is what it is. I mean,
coche favorito.  Es lo que es.  Quiero decir, simplemente me
I just I quite literally love the car.
encanta el coche.
So, beautiful car. I'm going to let you
Qué coche tan bonito.  Voy a dejar que ustedes lo
guys to absorb it. Look at the beauty of
asimilen.  Admira su belleza
it, and hopefully get motivated by it.
y, con suerte, inspírate en ella.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
[singing]
[cantando]
&gt;&gt; Also, I'm sure you guys can see in the
Además, estoy seguro de que ustedes también pueden ver al
background by now, too. As you can see,
fondo.  Como pueden ver,
the supercar garage is currently being
actualmente se está trabajando en el garaje de superdeportivos
worked [music] on. You know, beautiful,
[música].  Ya sabes,
beautiful things we have coming. We're
nos esperan cosas preciosas, preciosas.
going to have three cars here, another
Vamos a tener tres coches aquí, otro
car here. So, we're going to have four
coche aquí.  Así que vamos a tener cuatro
cars in the garage so they can be
coches en el garaje para que estén
comfortable. We're going to have couches
cómodos.  Vamos a tener sofás,
and tables and a bar and [__] TVs and
mesas, un bar, televisores y demás
[__] Then, if we come up here, we are
.  Luego, si subimos aquí,
currently going to be adding a nice
actualmente vamos a agregar un
little [music] railing system, of
pequeño y bonito sistema de barandilla [musical], por
course, nobody falls off to their
supuesto, nadie se caerá y
[__] death. But, this is going to be
morirá.  Pero aquí es
where I trade. So, I'll have my trading
donde voy a operar.  Así que tendré mi equipo de trading
set up here, 15 different monitors, TV
montado aquí, con 15 monitores diferentes y
screens so I can see the news and all
pantallas de televisión para poder ver las noticias y todas
the good [__] going on in the days. Name
las cosas buenas que pasan durante el día.  Nombra
a cooler setup than being able to be on
una configuración más genial que poder estar en
your computer, yada yada yada, take your
tu computadora, bla bla bla, hacer tus
trades, make millions of dollars like
operaciones, ganar millones de dólares como lo
you do every single day. That's what you
haces todos los días.  Eso es lo que
do. Check your bank account. Okay, $167
haces.  Revisa tu cuenta bancaria.  De acuerdo, 167
million in the bank. That's awesome.
millones de dólares en el banco.  Eso es genial.
Walk over here and just glance at your
Acércate y echa un vistazo a tus
beautiful, beautiful cars. Literal
preciosos coches.
chills. Literal chills thinking about
Escalofríos literales.  Literalmente se me pone la piel de gallina solo de pensarlo
it. Maybe puff on one of these little
.  Tal vez fumar una de estas pequeñas y
rare pinks. I've done it now.
raras rosas.  Ya lo he hecho.
Also, we have a staircase right here.
Además, tenemos una escalera justo aquí.
This one's going to end up leading up
Este pasillo acabará desembocando
into the actual upper part of the
en la parte superior del
warehouse which I never really showed
almacén, que nunca os he enseñado
you guys, but we're going to do a cigar
, pero vamos a montar un
bar lounge, whiskey bar lounge, all that
salón con bar de puros, un salón con bar de whisky y todo ese tipo de
cool stuff up here. It's going to be
cosas chulas aquí arriba.  Va a ser
very, very hip up there. People are
muy, muy moderno allá arriba.  A la gente le va a
going to love it. When I say people, I
encantar.  Cuando digo gente, me
mean the people watching cuz nobody's
refiero a la gente que está mirando, porque nadie está
invited except me. Now, I'd love
invitado excepto yo.  Ahora, me encantaría
[clears throat] to come back downstairs
[se aclara la garganta] volver a bajar aquí abajo
here. Well, the greatest thing about
.  Bueno, la verdad es que lo mejor de
being rich, honestly, is that I can do
ser rico es que puedo hacer
all of this [__] and know that it's just
todas estas cosas y saber que es solo
for me. Nobody's going to come here. I'm
para mí.  Nadie va a venir aquí.
not doing it to impress nobody. I just
No lo hago para impresionar a nadie.  Simplemente puedo
get to walk around and look at all of
caminar y mirar todas
the [__] that I bought and all of the
las cosas que compré y cómo todo el
hard work finally [music] paying off via
trabajo duro [de la música] finalmente da sus frutos a través de
cars, warehouses, houses, and all the
autos, almacenes, casas y todas las
finer things in life that I get to buy.
cosas buenas de la vida que puedo comprar.   Lo que más
That's my favorite part about being rich
me gusta de ser rico
is that I don't give a [__] what other
es que me importa un bledo lo que
people think and I do it because I love
piensen los demás y lo hago porque me encanta
it. Yes, sir. Anyways, probably going to
.  Sí, señor.  Bueno, probablemente termine
end up taking this for a spin, show you
dándole una vuelta, mostrándoles
guys what it looks like on the road, how
cómo se ve en la carretera, qué tan
loud it is, [music] and um again,
ruidoso es, [música] y, de nuevo,
hopefully this will motivate you guys to
espero que esto los motive a
be great. Everybody's got it in them.
ser geniales.  Todos lo llevan dentro.
But it's here. It's right here in your
Pero está aquí.  Está aquí mismo, en tu
heart. You got to really, really, really
corazón.  Tienes que desearlo de verdad, de verdad, de verdad
want it. You got to dig deep. You got to
.  Tienes que esforzarte al máximo.  Tienes que
work long nights. You got to be willing
trabajar muchas noches.  Tienes que estar dispuesto
to work a 9- 5 and then go home
a trabajar de 9 a 5 y luego irte a casa
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]
&gt;&gt; and also work from 5 to 9. That's what a
y también trabajar de 5 a 9. Eso es lo que
lot of people don't understand. You're
mucha gente no entiende.  Vas a estar
going to be working, working, working,
trabajando, trabajando, trabajando,
working and then it will finally pay
trabajando y luego finalmente dará sus frutos
off, pay off, pay off, pay off. So, keep
, dará sus frutos, dará sus frutos, dará sus frutos.  Así que, sigue adelante
on going. Let's get it.
.  Vamos a conseguirlo.
&gt;&gt; [music]
[música]